Once upon a time... can happen again.
Another Cinderella Story is a music, comedy, romance
film directed by Damon Santostefano.
A guy who danced with what could be the girl of his dreams at a costume ball only has one hint at her
identity: the Zune she left behind as she rushed home in order to make her curfew.
And with a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity in front of
him, he sets out to find his masked beauty.
Mary Santiago, played by Selena Gomez.
Joey Parker, played by Drew Seeley.
Dominique Blatt, played by Jane Lynch.
Bree, played by Katharine Isabelle.
Britt, played by Emily Perkins.
Tami, played by Jessica Parker Kennedy.
Another Cinderella Story is a 2008 American teen musical comedy film directed by
Damon Santostefano and written by Erik Patterson and Jessica Scott.
The film stars Selena Gomez, Drew Seeley, and Jane Lynch.
It is a stand-alone sequel to A Cinderella Story (2004) and the
second installment in the A Cinderella Story series.
Like the first film, it is a retelling of the
Cinderella fairy tale in a modern setting.
The film was released on DVD on September 16, 2008, and
premiered on ABC Family on January 18, 2009.
The film was followed by A Cinderella Story: Once Upon a Song (2011).
The film explores themes of high school, dance, dancer, fairy tale, masked ball.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.